哦  太好了  你在这儿  我必须要找人聊聊
Oh, good, you're here. I really need to talk.
噢  我洗耳恭听
Oh, I'm all ears.
好的  维罗在低谷期  她投不了球
Okay, Willow's in a slump and she can't pitch,
这会让她进不了学校垒球队的
and that's gonna keep her from making varsity softball.
体育运动  我不在行
Sports.
但是她投不了球的原因
But the reason she can't pitch
是因为她无法全神贯注于任何事
is because she can't concentrate on anything
一心只有她对乔伊的疯狂迷恋
other than her massive crush on Joey.
哦  感情  这东西我在行
Ooh, feelings. Yay.
维罗是个好苗子
Willow's just so awesome,
我希望她能意识到大千世界除了乔伊以外
and I wish she would realize that there's so much more out there
还有无数的新鲜玩意等着被发掘
in the world for her other than just Joey.
那就让她看看大千世界的新鲜玩意啊
Okay, so make her see that there's more out there.
在她的储物柜里留一张匿名者的情书
Put a love note from a secret admirer
她就会把乔伊忘得一干二净的
in her locker, and she'll forget all about Joey.
丽芙  这个主意棒极了
Liv, that's actually a really good idea.
事实上  我还记得四年级时
Actually, I remember in fourth grade
当我沉湎于马基·斯蒂文而不能自拔时
when I was so obsessed with marky Stevens
我简直都玩不好儿童足球了
that I literally couldn't even play kickball.
之后我收到了一封匿名情书  写信的原来是
And then I got a secret admirer note from...
你
You.
之后谁在学校儿童足球赛
And who went on to win top prize
独占鳌头了啊
in the school kickball-y thing?
别说了  不用谢
Uh-huh, you're welcome.